3 MILLION CHANNEL SUBSCRIBERS
CELEBRATION EVENT
SUMERAGI IKON
Hello-Iko, everyone! I'm Ikonic!
Hello-Iko!
Thank you all for coming to my three
million subs celebration concert today!
I even got a new outfit just for this.
Do you recognize this pattern?
So much has happened on the way here.
It was hard and I wanted to
quit so many times.
Ikon!
You can do it!
There's a reason
I've stuck with it, though.
Hey,
I know you're watching.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Bye-Iko!
THIS STREAM HAS ENDED
Things are looking up lately.
SUMERAGI IKON CHAT STREAM!
SUMERAGI IKON - 32.2K SUBSCRIBERS
My sub count is growing, too.
With this number, I can easily
be considered a top VTuber.
Huh? You landed tickets
to the Blue Box concert?
Blue Box? What's that?
Huh? They're the number one
VTuber group in Japan, you know.
Their biggest star, Momotose Ao,
recently crossed three million subs.
VTubers doing concerts
in Chiba Messe? Sign of the times.
Three million...?
At my current pace,
it'll take around a century
for me to hit three million.
Am I actually the furthest one
from her dream out of all four of us?
Wh-Wh-What do I do?
I'm gonna be the black sheep!
I have no doubt Rikka, Nene, and Shinobu
will make their dreams come true.
I'll get left behind...
I never would've had
these thoughts before.
What's gotten into me?
Meowrgh!
What's wrong, Kirino?
Something on your mind?
This is all your fault.
You jerk!
My fault?
She can execute a good tackle.
That's your takeaway?
I can't be satisfied with the status quo.
I need to get more popular.
MOMOTOSE AO - 3 MILLION SUBSCRIBERS
Momotose Ao, one of
the biggest VTubers around.
She's what I should strive to be.
I gotta catch up to her quick.
I'll do some research into her
and figure out what I'm lacking.
Welcome to my three million subs
celebration concert!
I hope you all enjoy yourselves!
She's...
She's such a good dancer!
Her 3D model is pretty
and the effects are out of this world!
Wait, it's too early for me to go 3D.
I should focus on her regular streams.
I'm making macarons today.
I hear it's hard even for pros,
but I'll try my best.
PIANO STREAM!
VTUBER TACKLES CENTRALIZED COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAM
Wow.
I do a wide variety of content too,
but she's on a different level.
It's not fair that she's smart, too!
No, stop getting cold feet.
I gotta outdo Ao-chan in something.
MUNDEY
A notification for Kirino's stream?
A cooking stream? Now that's new.
COOKING STREAM!
SUMERAGI IKON
Hello-Iko!
I'm gonna try baking a cake today!
Here's what I'm making.
A special four-tier cake!
No VTuber's ever done this before.
Let's get started.
First, open this pack
of superfine sugar...
Uh, where's the mixer?
WHAT DO I WATCH?
WHERE'S THE HANDCAM?
Body temperature?
How do I figure that out?
How do I preheat an oven?
A heatproof bowl? There are
bowls that aren't heatproof?
Wait, I don't have a handcam,
so you can't see what I'm doing, huh?
THIS LIVESTREAM HAS ENDED
Bye-Iko for now!
What is she doing?!
Chat is confused as heck!
SUGAR UNPACKING STREAM
F FOR STREAM
HOME EC. ROOM
Yikes.
That was a disaster.
But I can't beat Ao-chan
unless I one-up her.
CHOOSEDEY
Hello-Iko!
I'm playing an instrument called
the didgeridoo today.
WHENSDEY
I'll get a perfect score on
a Tokyo U mock exam today.
THIRSTDEY
I'll keep singing until
I hit three million subs.
FRYDEY
Good morning, everybody.
Hey, Kirino.
We need to talk—hey, wait!
Why are you running?
'Cause you're gonna yell at me!
Just leave me alone!
If I don't do this,
I won't be able to beat Ao-chan!
What are you saying?
Ao-chan, huh? I see how it is.
Bucky'll definitely try
to stop me if I tell him.
He'll say, "There's no way you
could ever beat Momotose Ao."
I gotta figure this out on my own.
What do I have to do to beat Ao-chan?
Ao-chan's streaming.
MOMOTOSE AO NEW OUTFIT
KINDA SEXY <3
This...
This is it.
FEW DAYS LATER
Check this out.
IKON NEW OUTFIT DEBUT!
Iko's doing a new outfit stream.
That's pretty sudden.
So she hasn't come to club because
she's been busy drawing this.
Wow, I can't wait.
NEW OUTFIT DEBUT
It's always fun trying to figure out
what it looks like from the silhouette.
Oh, here we go.
Hello-Iko, everyone!
What do you think of my new outfit?
A swimsuit?!
Wow, that's steamy.
Is she really doing this?
VIEWERS
Wow...
Look at that viewer count go.
Maybe because I made it way
more risque than Ao-chan's.
WOW, IKON!
I COULD WATCH THIS FOREVER.
Th-This is amazing.
Huh?
JUMP FOR US!
You want me to jump?
Okay, I'll jump for mew.
Hey, she's jumping.
Wow, they actually bounce and sway.
Uh, it's still going?
The angle of her neck went all wonky, too.
Did something go wrong?
What in the world are you doing?
I'm streaming! Give it back right meow!
I can't beat Ao-chan in anything!
I can't catch up unless I do this.
I see. I can't say I approve.
There's no need for you to play catch-up.
You already have what it takes
to be a top VTuber.
Liar.
I'm not lying. Yours truly would
never lie to comfort somebody.
You've fried your brain over this, right?
Just leave the rest to me.
After all, you're not at all
inferior to Momotose Ao.
Okay. Help, Bucky.
Sure thing! You can count on yours truly!
Your face...
Hmm? You noticed, too?
Just how perfect my skin is?!
I'm saying it's too close!
You gave that cool speech earlier, Bucky,
but do you really think
I can beat Ao-chan?
A Yamabuki never flatters.
You do have that potential.
How? She's better than me at everything.
Well...
First of all, I love your voice.
L-Love?!
Yes, I love it.
A VTuber's voice is one of
their most valuable assets.
O-Oh, right, yeah. My voice.
Visuals, voice, creativity.
Naturally, you won't gain popularity
if you're lacking in any of those,
but personally, voice is
the most important to me.
With long streams, people do other stuff
while watching them on the side.
It becomes an audio-only
experience at that point,
and if they don't like your voice,
they can't listen to it for long.
On that note, you have
a low-key angelic voice.
It's calming and I can
listen to it all day.
That alone is a top-tier
talent for a VTuber.
I believe that your voice
is superior to Momotose Ao's.
Slow down on the praise!
I'm literally clenching
my cheeks right now!
Like I said, I don't flatter. I mean it.
However, having a great voice
means nothing without reach.
That's where collaborating
with bigger streamers comes in.
[SURPRISE COLLAB] TAKOYAKI PARTY!
You should join
their livestreams as a guest.
Once people hear your voice,
they're sure to take an interest in you.
But...
Would anyone even collab with me?
I looked into it.
I'LL DM THE VTUBERS I WANT FOR THAT ONE EVENT! PLEASE DON'T IGNORE IT!
This is Konpiler, a VTuber
with over 150k subscribers.
She's recruiting participants
on social media for an event.
What's this event?
RESULTS
Speedrunning a horror game, it seems.
She's personally contacting VTubers
who post a good time on stream.
What do you say to giving it a shot?
Okay, let's do it.
That's the spirit. Then...
We'll need time to practice the game,
so let's do the stream one week from now.
Okay.
Anyway...
Regardless of the results,
I'm proud of you for trying new things.
In the past, you only
ever did chat streams.
I had a dream.
A dream?
A dream where my dream came true.
Oh? What did you see?
I'm not telling you!
Phweh! Phweh!
Grr! How vexing!
I won't tell you, but...
I'LL SHOW YOU SOMEDAY
ONE WEEK LATER
Hello-Iko, everyone.
Today, I'm doing the horror game
speedrun that's been trending online.
I'm nervous because it's my first time
streaming a horror game.
This is a super short game...
I've watched most of Kirino's gaming
streams, and she's got skills.
This is a typical FPS where you
shoot zombies down as you advance.
The genre she's best at.
It's highly likely she'll get
picked for the event.
Go, Kirino! Shoot those zombies
for the sake of your dreams!
I'll take this gun here, craft
some healing items in advance,
and trigger this trap here!
I'll dodge it with a roll!
She's the type to move while gaming, huh?
She's making good time.
She'll be fine if she keeps this up.
Stay away, you stupid zombie!
Oh no! I'm gonna get eaten!
My bloodline will end with me!
Hey, don't let go of your controller.
Didn't you practice for this?
Here, controller.
I just can't handle horror.
You hit me right in the philtrum!
I can't! I'm gonna wet myself!
If I wet myself, that's the end of me!
Yikes, Yamabuki-kun's making
Iko play a horror game.
Wow, what an idiot.
Iko's allergy to horror is no joke.
Well, you got a bunch of comments
and gained subscribers.
I'm not getting that
collab invite, though.
Not if you can't play the game, no.
Then it's all meaningless.
You helped me out, but I blew it.
How could I fail so badly?
Everyone has strengths and weaknesses.
It's my bad for not checking
with you. Forgive me.
I said I'd show you my dream,
but I don't think I'll ever be able to.
You gave me all that praise,
but I just had to go screw it all up.
I see. The VTuber world
sure is fascinating.
Kirino, why do you think the amateur
Koshien is more popular than pro baseball?
Lots of people with a shaved head fetish?
No more ridiculous theories, please.
The efforts of the young players,
the drama leading up to the tournament,
the twists and turns caused
by their inexperience.
Skills and mastery alone
can't move a person's heart.
That goes for VTubers, too.
If your efforts and feelings
make an impression,
people will fall in love with you.
Sometimes, even your flaws
can be an asset.
They can?
A compilation video
of your stream is trending!
Huh?!
No way! Why?
SUMERAGI IKON STREAM COMPILATION - 270K VIEWS
Your over-the-top freakout
must've gone over well.
You made an impression precisely
because of your dislike of horror.
Konpiler may very well take notice.
Oh, so it was okay to be a scaredy-cat.
What kinda clips did
that compilation have?
Want to watch it?
ROOKIE VTUBER WETS HERSELF FROM FEAR
Hey, I didn't wet myself!
Well, thumbnails need to be eye-catching.
No way I'm getting invited now!
Never say never.
See? Your phone's buzzing.
Maybe Konpiler has sent you an invite.
Meow! Like heck it is!
MOMOTOSE AO COLLAB INVITATION
A BOLT FROM THE BLUE
Wh-Wh-Wha...
What do I do, Bucky?!
C-C-Calm down, Kirino!
It's a collab invite from
the top VTuber Momotose Ao!
We get to interact with that
three-million-sub monster so soon?
Even yours truly can't help
but be thrilled!
This is our chance to make
Kirino known across Japan!
I can't just collab
with Ao-chan right away!
Read it closely!
You'll just be one of many at first!
The Ao Cup is a game tourney
with over 50 VTubers taking part,
and the cream of the crop
will get to challenge her.
Only when you get past the qualifiers
will you interact with her.
This edition of the Ao Cup is
a Meow Drive racing tourney.
I'm real good at this one!
Great.
Conquer the prelims and get
some screentime with Momotose Ao!
Yeah, I'll do my best.
My hyper best!
Okay, time for some special training!
FEW DEYS LATER
Hell-ao! The Ao Cup is here!
We'll have heated battles in order
to challenge me one-on-one!
We've got familiar faces
as well as dark-horse newbies.
None of the races are staged,
so cheer them all on.
Now, let me announce
the groups for the prelims.
I-It's started.
First off, we have the special Group A.
This group is where we quarantine
all the problem children!
Wh-What?!
They've been blacklisted
by other agencies
or are so problematic, they have
banhammers hanging right over their heads.
Even among them, keep an eye out for...
Sumeragi Ikon-chan!
She's a super problematic VTuber
who wet herself on a stream!
I didn't wet myself!
Did she invite Kirino as a joke?
Hey, am I gonna get a reward for winning?
Give me all your subs!
I'll give you a kiss if you win.
Don't want it, uggo!
I'd rather get a kiss from Ikon-chan!
Ikon-chan's kissing face
in three, two, one...
H-Huh?
Mwah...
She's uggo, too!
This is her kissing face?
Are you taking
a leak right now, Ikon-chan?
I don't have many expressions.
This is the best I can do.
You're not fooling anybody!
You're taking the piss for sure!
Crap!
Kirino gains nothing from
hanging around this vulgar bunch!
It's true!
Kirino, just focus on winning!
I know you can do this!
It's to show them the fruits
of all your practice!
Ded...
Bwahaha, I win!
SUMERAGI IKON - 4TH PLACE OUT OF 4
You just got lucky with the items!
Sorry, Bucky. I lost.
It is what it is. Contests can
be decided by luck at times.
We'll have to bid farewell
to all the people who lost.
The winners, please move
to this waiting room.
Yours truly lost? Not to mention
we were dead last.
I should've researched the game more.
No, before that, I should've
foreseen this kind of treatment!
What an utter disgrace I am!
A Yamabuki is supposed to be
no less than perfect!
I'm sorry, Kirino. This is all my fault.
They...
They were so awesome!
I can't believe how good they were!
Sure, I wasn't able to talk to Ao-chan,
but I'm glad I got to be a part of this.
Wait, Kirino, don't you hate
how you were treated?
Yeah, it was frustrating
that I couldn't get back at them...
But more than that,
I'm happy that our hard work
got us such a big stage.
It made me believe that together, we can
make even more amazing things happen!
I've never thought of it that way before.
It seems I was too fixated on results.
What's most important is
that you had fun.
Well? Did you have fun?
Yep!
Good to hear. However...
I can't let those jerks get away
with the crap they gave you!
How dare they hurt my Kirino
right in front of me?!
And Momotose Ao invited you and
didn't even interact with you! How rude!
Listen up, Kirino!
We're trying again!
Next time, we'll make direct
contact with Momotose Ao!
Huh? Uh...
Say, Bucky, did you just...
Whoa!
Ao-chan's calling!
MOMOTOSE AO
What?! Let me have a word with her!
No, Bucky! Shh!
Hello?
MOMOTOSE AO
Hello, this is Momotose Ao.
I'm actually contacting all the entrants,
so I'm sorry I couldn't call you sooner.
It's t-t-totally fine.
It was s-s-such an honor
to have you invite me!
Sorry about today.
I put you in that group
because I thought it'd be funny,
but they took it a bit too far.
I really didn't mind! I-I'd love to
collab with you again one day!
I'll reach out again.
Just like this time,
I hope you'll bring your advisor with you.
The reason you've grown so much lately
is because you have
a capable brain behind you, no?
I'd love to speak to your
advisor directly next time.
MOMOTOSE AO
See you then!
CALL ENDED
Bucky! How'd she know about you?!
No way.
Was she able to detect my involvement
just from the content of the videos?
I see.
So this is what the top
of the top VTuber is like.
I still have a long way to go.
But one day, I'll surely...
What's the matter, Kirino?
You really caught me
off guard back there.
What do you mean?
What?
Wait, that face...
So was that a k...
No, it wasn't.
This is my "I wanna use
the restroom" face.
Restroom?
You made my heart race a little.
"How dare they hurt my Kirino," you said.
Whoa, wait!
Forgive me! It was a rush
of blood to the head!
It was a slip of the tongue! I'm sorry!
I'll do my best.
Like you said earlier,
there won't be so much distance
between us next time.
WE'LL MAKE DIRECT CONTACT
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Sriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard
Quality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon